flymna.com 2016-06-16

# Privacy Policy | Myanmar National Airlines

This Privacy Policy advises how we use your personal information. In it, we explain the types of personal information we collect, how we collect it, what we use it for and who we may share your personal information with.

### What this Privacy Policy covers

This Privacy Policy covers all personal information about you that we collect, use and otherwise process in connection with your relationship with Myanmar National Airlines as a customer or potential customer. By “Personal Information” we mean information about you where you are, or could be, identified, such as your name and contact details, your travel arrangements and purchase history and information about your access to our websites.

### When do we collect personal information?

We collect personal information about you whenever you use our services (whether services provided directly by us or by other companies or agents acting on our behalf), when you travel with us, when you use our websites or use our call centres or mobile applications.

### What types of personal information do we collect?

We collect personal information about you, your travel arrangements, how you use our services and how you use our websites, call centres and mobile applications. This may include information that you provide to us directly, or through companies or agents we work with, as well as information which we collect when you use our services.

### What do we use your personal information for?

  * To provide the travel and other services you have asked us to provide.
  * To personalise your travel experience.
  * To communicate with you about the travel and other services you have asked us to provide.
  * To provide you with up to the minute information and upcoming offersfrom us (where we have your permission to do so).
  * To improve our services.
  * For security purposes.

### Who do we share your personal information with?

Your personal information may be shared within the group of companies we work with.  
In order to facilitate your travel arrangements, we will often need to share your personal information with third parties including other airlines and airport operators, customs and immigration authorities, travel agents involved in making your travel arrangements. We may also share your information with our customer loyalty partners, when you transfer between airlines or use a hotel to earn Miles. We also share your personal information with third parties who deliver services either to you or to us, such as companies that provide airport assistance or marketing agencies.  
We do not sell personal information to third parties.

### How we look after the policy

We will keep this Privacy Policy under review and notify you of any changes by posting the revised policy on flymna.com, to take effect as soon as it is posted

### Cookie Policy

This site uses cookies – small text files that are placed on your machine to help the site provide a better user experience. In general, cookies are used to retain user preferences, store information for things like shopping carts, and provide anonymised tracking data to third party applications like Google Analytics. As a rule, cookies will make your browsing experience better. However, you may prefer to disable cookies on this site and on others. The most effective way to do this is to disable cookies in your browser. We suggest consulting the Help section of your browser or taking a look at the About Cookies website which offers guidance for all modern browsers.
